48ers.com 2015-12-07

# 48ers - Privacy Policy

We built 48ers to make it easy to search the social network space, not to sell your information on to third parties. That's why we follow the simple rules outlined below. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service at any time. If we make changes, we will indicate at the top of this page the policy's modification date. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. By using and continuing to use our Web site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not provide your personal details to us. 

48ers.com is registered to and operated by Zamzar Ltd in England as a limited company (number 6463494).

**This policy is effective from 1st May 2010**

**This policy was last modified on 1st May 2010**

48ers is registered with the UK [Information Commissioner's Office (ICO)](http://www.ico.gov.uk/) in the [Register of Data Controllers](http://www.ico.gov.uk/tools_and_resources/register_of_data_controllers.aspx) (under the company name of Zamzar) as required by the UK's 1998 Data Protection Act. The entry in the register is available for public inspection to help ensure transparency and openness in the processing of your data.

For each visitor to our Web page, IP addresses are logged and used by 48ers for measuring usage.

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

We may also store information about you using cookies (files sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our site in future. We do this to track patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site and to store the preferences of users. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may also place or recognize cookies on your browser.

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. To learn more about "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

In the course of providing the Services data is transferred to and from servers located in the United States. By agreeing to 48er's Terms of Service you accept the transfer of such data as is necessary to provide the Services.
